<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.magicsearch" name="Magic Search and Editor" version="1.0.0" provider-name="fnord12">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Improved search results for actors and more. Field editor.</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">An actor/director search engine and metadata editor.  See sample DialogVideoInfo.xml file included in Skins folder for how to call.

-Displays search criteria in search results list.
-Includes Writer credit in actor/director search results.
-List the results chronologically instead of alphabetically.  This gives a feel more like IMDb or Wikipedia.
-Integrates Movie, TV, and Episode results.  See a chronological listing of all an actor's appearances, regardless of the medium (again, similar to IMDb).
-Suppress listings for Episodes when the actor already appears in the TV Show.
-Display the Role (and/or director/writer) in the results list.
-In general, allows skinning of what fields appear in the search.
- Sort actors by Order field, or by Name or Role
-Also allows for searches in other fields.    As seen in sample DialogVideoInfo, can click on Studio to do a Studio search.  Can click on genre or year to get a list of all movies/tvshows in that genre for the given year.

As metadata editor:
-Edit actor details
-Add or delete actor
-Edit year, genre, studio, plot (in a tiny box, sorry), etc.
-See included sample DialogVideoInfo.xml to see how to call it.
</description>
<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Warnings:#1 Uses direct SQL calls and may require special configuration for non-standard Kodi database.  #2 Causes Kodi to crash on rare occasions.  See readme file.</disclaimer>


		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		
		<source>https://github.com/fnord12/script.magicsearch</source>
		<forum></forum>
		
		<news>Initial release.</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
</extension>
</addon>



